a fraction of your dose daily with GH in
the muscle will work so much better.
The the next point that I want to get on
to uh back when I first started
treatment uh the one of the only people
who I could find online to help me many
many years ago was the late Dr. John
Pris and right before he passed away he
was very big on this idea of uh daily
TRT and HCG injections and I'm not a fan
of the hCG stuff but what he was talking
about was the idea of combining the TRT
and the hCG in one syringe so that you
can do the shot together and when I saw
you talking about growth hormone and TRT
in the same syringe I was like well that
makes complete sense to me and it's very
interesting when you put up these videos
and you see people require saying oh you
can't mix TRT and and growth hormone in
the same syringe because one's an oil
and one's a water. It's like we're not
trying to make a homogeneous solution of
the two. You push the plunger and one
will go in and the other one will go in
and they'll say, "Oh, you can't do
that." And I'm like, "Well, it does.
>> I just did, bitch."
>> Like, I just did.
>> Like, you might not be able to, but it's
not that complicated. So the this the
reason why I I like when you brought
this up and it was just this light bulb
moment to me is that as someone who
naturally has an IGF-1 over 300, growth
hormone has never personally really been
on my radar, right?
>> But when guys are looking at growth
hormone, the big barrier to entry, you
know, from their perception is going,
"Oh, well, I don't want to do a daily
shot." But if you're already doing a TRT
daily and you want to take growth
hormone, this to me is like the most
efficient way to get the most optimal
protocol. So could you explain to guys
one why you can put them in the same
syringe and put them into the deltoid
not into the subcutaneous fat and also
why the combination of testosterone and
growth hormone is much better for
optimizing not just growth in the gym
but also health and longevity than just
testosterone at work.
>> All right. So okay let's we got two
divergent populations. Let's say you're
19 years old. Your body makes test. Your
body makes GH you don't need either. Now
let's say you're 40 years old. your body
doesn't make G doesn't release GH
anymore and it doesn't make test really
anymore. You need both period and it's
that's the goal is to get your IGF-1 at
least to 300 because that's the medical
cut off for safety. Is there really any
danger going over 300? I don't think so
because the medical community is really
dumb and they confabulate something that
is a
growth promoting agent with a cancer
promoting agent under the opice that
well if you have cancer the cancer is
going to grow faster. I was like yeah
but if you have cancer you already have
cancer. Growing it faster means you
detect it quicker and you'll be able to
cut it out faster before you're so old
you won't survive cutting it out. Also,
testosterone also increases IGF-1. So,
if you want to avoid cancer, don't use
testosterone. Also, eating protein
increases IGF-1. So, if you want to
prevent yourself from getting cancer,
don't eat protein. Also, lifting weights
increases IGF-1. So, if you don't want
to grow cancer, don't lift weights. So,
the whole point is any single thing that
increases
muscle also will increase cancer. Now,
one person brought up some [__]
study that, well, they showed that if
you lift weights, it decreases cancer
growth speeds. It's like, yeah,
basically, if you lift weights, you're
healthy. If you're healthy, you've got
natural killer cells. And if you've got
natural killer cells, you'll be able to
fight cancer in your body. My point
isn't don't lift weights, this [__]
[__] that I just had to address how
stupid these people are in the comment
section. The point is is that everything
you're doing causes you to grow cancer.
If you live in America, breathing the
air causes you to get cancer. What do
you call it? Drinking the water causes
you to get cancer. Eating the food
causes you to get cancer. The
testosterone you're injecting causes you
to get cancer. Lifting weights, eating
protein, everything causes cancer.
Growth hormone just increases IGF-1. And
IGF-1 is a way that cancer can grow. But
it's not the only way that cancer can
grow. Everything you do can cause. If
you grow muscle, you're growing cancer,
too. If you have cancer, if you don't
have cancer that it can't grow because
you don't have it. So the goal would be
if you're really worried about getting
cancer, you should be drinking filtered
water. You should be breathing purified
air. You should be eating organic food.
You know, you should be doing
everything. You should probably should
move to Europe or Colombia or a
civilized country where they actually
have regulations and the food's not
toxic waste. But the point is is if you
live in America, you're going to get
cancer. It's just a matter of time
because of how toxic the entire
environment is here. So
the idea of avoiding growth hormone and
aging faster to avoid getting cancer is
[__] So now that we've established
everybody who's over 40 and probably a
lot of people younger than 40 should be
on growth hormone because your body
slows down the growth hormone production
after 20. So, you're growing until
you're 20. Then you're aging slow from
20 to 40. Then your growth hormone gets
cut in half again. You're aging really
fast between 40 and 60. And then you
have pretty much no growth hormone at
all after 60. And your body is just
supposed to [__] die because the
whole point of humans is to procreate.
It's humans ex like all animals. Humans
are just animals. I know you think
you're special. You're not. You're just
an animal and you're supposed to create
baby humans. That's it. And once you're
not pumping out baby humans, you're
supposed to die because you're taking up
resources that could go towards other
humans that are growing or reproducing.
But by the time you're 40, you're not
going to be making more kids. Especially
if you're a woman, there's no point in
you existing anymore. So, you're still
functionally useful. Like, you can chop
wood, maybe you can groom kids or take
care of horses or some [__] in the tribe
up until 60. But after 60, people were
just [__] useless. So, you're just
supposed to die. But guess what? We live
in a civilized culture now where we can
have great lives from 40 to 80 like
Sylvester Stallone. And how does
Sylvester Stallone do that? He used
[__] growth hormone. That if you
start taking growth hormone at 25 or 30
and you take a hormone replacement dose.
People are so [__] dumb. They're
like, I don't want my forehead to get
big. It's like, does your kids have a
big forehead? [__] nuts. Because your
kids have a high growth hormone level,
[__] [__] It's like, does your kids
have cancer? No, shut the [__] up about
the cancer and the side effects that you
just replace what's missing and you keep
that going and you're going to age
slower. People like that's not true.
They found in rats. Rats died of cancer
faster. It's like they took rats that
are genetically predesigned to get
cancer called windstrol rats and then
they're like don't use growth hormone
populace because look it showed these
rats got cancer. It's like you took the
rats that are automatically going to get
cancer and you gave it something to make
the cancers they already had grow
faster, you [__] liars. And that's
how these studies dupe the public is
that you have people who are uneducated
reading the abstract and then making
YouTube videos about it and then your
dumbass believes it and that's how you
get duped. It's propaganda. But that's
funny is they're using you to promote
the propaganda. So you actually come
across as sincere. You're just [__]
So you believe everything you're told
like about two masks if you're in the
United States. These stupid [__] wore
two masks. It's like they got well one
face diaper is not going to do it. I
know. I'm gonna put two face diapers on.
It's like let me ask you something face
diaper crusader. Do you ever wear a
[__] condom? No. So for 40 years
you've been [__] girls without a
condom, but now you're going to put a
diaper on your face to breathe the air.
That's how [__] stupid Americans are.
So, the growth hormone, if you keep your
level at approximately where you were at
20 or maybe 30, you're going to age
slower. And there's two terms for aging.
There's longevity, which is lifespan.
Then there's vitality, which is health
span. So, maybe you're going to die at
85, no matter what the [__] you do.
Maybe you're in the movie Final
Destination, and you're the Grim
Reaper's coming for you at 85 years old.
You could be like Sylvester Stallone at
80 or you could be like Stephen Hawkins
at 50 and the difference is growth
hormone and testosterone. So the growth
hormone amplifies the androgen receptors
response to testosterone binding
and the testosterone
amplifies the GH receptor receiving the
GH. It also testosterone converts into
estrogen which when it binds to estrogen
beta receptor upregulates the conversion
of the GH to IGF-1 and the testosterone
inhibits the smatastatin which blocks
the GH. So people will say estrogen
doesn't cause an incre like that same
[__] liar who says he's a doctor.
He's like estrogen doesn't cause an
increase in IGF-1 because women don't
have it. It's because women don't have
testosterone and testosterone it blocks
the myostatin. So without blocking the
myostatin then the estrogen is not going
to do what it needs to do that the
estrogen alpha receptor is going to
cause more somatastatin to be released
and the estrogen beta receptor is going
to upregulate IGF-1 production but
because the beta receptor and the IGF-1
production is downstream of blocking
that GH receptor the estrogen alpha
receptor predominates over that. But
when you have testosterone, the
testosterone blocks the somatastatin,
which obiates the estrogen alpha
receptor binding, making it kind of
irrelevant and allows the estrogen beta
receptor to do its thing of converting
the GH to the IGF-1. Is it more
complicated than this? Yes. Is calories
a factor? Yes. Is insulin a factor? Yes.
So, having a higher carb diet, you're
going to grow more muscle than a low
carb diet, but a higher carb diet is
going to grow more cancer than a low
carb diet. That's why for a long time
keto diets were a great way adjunctively
treating cancer is on top of the
chemotherapy, radiotherapy and excision
surgeries, you could just decrease the
carb content of the person's diet and
the cancer would grow slower.
So by putting the GH and the test
together, you minimize the shots. So
there's people like, "I don't want to do
daily shots." I'm like, "Don't you use
GH?" Like, "Yeah." I was like, "So, you
already do daily shots?" Like, "Yeah."
So, so put the test in the same [__]
syringe as the GH [__] nuts. And then be
like, "Oh, I didn't think of that, but I
can't use that. It's it's it's a insulin
syringe." It's like you use a 27 gauge
insulin syringe. It draws right up. And
then there's all these [__] who want
to use back loing because it makes the
needle dull. It's like, "Oh my god,
dude. If that hurts that bad, do you
even [__] lift weights?" I can't
imagine someone taking sets to failure.
but then bitching because the needle was
dull. It's like you're taking drugs to
be more manly, but you can't handle the
shot. That's so counter like
it doesn't make any sense. The whole
point is you want to be more masculine.
Well, masculine men don't whine about
pain. They embrace it because the more
pain makes you tougher. So, it just
boggles my mind these soft people like
they're it's basically like the
weightlifting gloves that you don't see
or the people who run their oils under
hot water to make it thinner so it hurts
less. Like a baby like a baby a baby's
got to have warm milk that these guys
are like babies. They have to have warm
oils injected in their butt. So, the the
whole point of injecting the glute is
that the glute's a big muscle so it
absorbs more. They tested this on
70-year-old dudes. The 70-year-old dudes
didn't have deltoids or triceps. Old
men, if you've ever dissected a human,
old men have paper thin muscles. Like
like paper thin muscles. Like I don't
even know how to describe it. It's so
you could grasp it. Like you ever go to
like get go to like Costco or go to
Walmart and get the Oscar Meyer baloney?
The Oscar Meyer bologna is all marbled
with fat and it's paper thin. That's
what a normal old person's muscle looks
like when you take them apart. So on
someone who actually has a delt or an
actual tricep, [__] will absorb just
[__] fine. And then it doesn't need
to be that long of a needle. And again,
the insulin needle is going to work. A
27 gauge halfinch needle is going to
work unless you're super [__] fat.
Then you can't even inject there. If
you're that fat, you shouldn't be doing
steroids anyway because the aromatized
enzyme exists in the fat. So the
injecting the fat is so dumb because
you're basically begging for the
testosterone to get converted to aromat
into estrogen. And people are going to
say, well, they found that daily
injection subcutaneous
had less estrogen conversion. It's not
because it was subcutaneous, [__]
It's because it was daily. They
confabulated the data to prove the
narrative they wanted to push. They
compared sporadic injections into
muscular to daily subcutaneous
injections and then incorrectly
attributed the difference to the
location of the shot, not the frequency
of the shot because they're [__]
terrible scientists. So, putting it in
the same syringe, the testosterone and
the um GH
will be more convenient because you'll
only have to give yourself seven shots a
week instead of 14. And is there a
reason to use test without GH? If you've
got a natural IGF-1 of 300, you don't
need GH. If is there a reason to use GH
without test? It's like, yeah, if your
IGF-1 is like a 100 and your natural
test is a thousand, then you don't need
test. But that ain't you. You wouldn't
be watching this channel if that was
you. So you basically 20 milligrams of
test and two units of DH. If you do it
daily, I get [__] up to a 1500
test in the blood with only like a 50 to
70 DHT and only like a 40 to 50
estradiol. And I get their IGF-1 up to
300 all day long. And that's simply by
using a fraction of the dose daily with
GH. that a fraction of your dose daily
with GH in the muscle will work so much
better than your Mr. Magcoo [__]
doctor giving you two shots of a 100 a
week. Sorry Dave, that was it. That's
the whole spiel.